http://www.beyond.com.au/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Beyond International respects your privacy. We have established this Web site for entertainment purposes and we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information.
Any and all information collected on our sites (www.beyond.com.au & others) will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, leased, loaned, traded, or otherwise disclosed to a third party.
Any information you give on this site will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. In general, you can surf this site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name and e-mail address. We intend to let you know before we collect personal information from you on the Internet. Content
Material presented on our sites do not represent warranties or endorsements of any product or service but mere statement of facts as known at the time of publication. Submissions
If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet - in order for us to reply to you, process an order or provide you with information, for example - we promise that you will know exactly how we intend to use such information. We will not publish your name on this Web site without your permission. We will not publish your e-mail address on this Web site. We will not distribute this information to others. If you tell us that you do not wish to receive additional information from us, we will respect your wishes.
We do not want to receive confidential or proprietary information from you through our Web site. Please note that any information or material sent to this Web site is deemed not to be confidential. By sending any information or material, Beyond International has an unrestricted, irrevocable license to use, reproduce, display, perform, modify, transmit and distribute those materials or information, and you also agree that Beyond International are free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques that you send us for any purpose. Collecting information
Some information about your IP address, Web browser, and computer operating system are automatically transmitted to our Web servers as an integral part of the operation of the Internet. Some of this information is used for demographic purposes as a technical resource to help us better serve our Web site visitors. We analyze this data for trends and statistics, and then we discard it. Our Web site logs are not personally identifiable and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals that actually browse the site. Use of cookies
Other information may be sent to your computer in the form of an Internet "cookie" to allow our Web server to better serve files to you.
The cookie is stored on your hard drive, along with others sent from other Web sites. Our server may request that your computer return a cookie to it, so that it "remembers" you as a user, and can better serve you. These return cookies, which may contain information supplied by you, are never stored on our server. Your Web browser can be set to allow you to refuse cookies. This will not lessen your ability to enjoy this Web site in any way, though it may slow performance in some cases. E-mail lists
Visitors must request to join a mailing list by completing a form on this site. We maintain email lists for the press and interested Web site visitors to inform them of new information on this Web site. We do not sell, reuse, rent, lease, loan, trade or otherwise divulge the addresses on our lists to anyone. In addition, we configure our list server software to refuse to divulge the e-mail addresses of our subscribers to anyone but authorized staff, including other list subscribers. Online transactions
If you place an order on this site, we must collect information from you including your credit card number and contact information. This information will be used by Beyond International and its' fulfillment partners solely to fulfill your order. Third party merchants displayed on this site are for your convenience, Beyond International may receive a referral fee for any transactions that occur though these links. Information given to third party merchants is not covered by this privacy statement. and users should make themselves aware of the policies of each third party site featured. Children's submissions
Features on this site are accessible to children under age 13. Any forms for comments or interactive content will only ask for e-mail addresses or demographic information with prior parental consent. Collected information will be used solely to directly respond to the child's request, not to contact the child for other purposes. E-mail addresses are only used for responses and are never sold, reused, rented, leased, loaned, traded, or otherwise disclosed to a third party, regardless of age. Names and e-mail addresses may be retained for legal purposes only, as permission to publish. We keep no other permanent record of children's names and e-mail addresses.
This Web site contains links to other Web sites. Beyond International is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
